(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
AmaneKanata 3DLIVE
2025.04.22 21:00 START
重大告知あり！！
Amane Kanata 3D LIVE
2025.04.22 21:00 START
Major Announcement Included!!
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
あ、悩める人の子よ
Ah, you troubled children of man,
人ならざるものも
And those who are not human as well,
たゆまず目指せよ
Aim for it without faltering,
いつでも一途な私で
As the me who is always single-minded.
ねえ、逸らした過去も
Hey, the past you looked away from,
退屈な未来も
And the boring future too,
カウンセリング やれやれ
I'll counsel them, good grief.
古今東西 ピースピース
Peace peace, all times and places!
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
ね、ね、ね、ね、ね
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
なんだかどうしても戦ってるような
It feels like, for some reason, I'm fighting,
そんな気がするの
That's just how it feels to me.
過去の自分 自分 自分 自分と
With my past self, myself, myself, myself.
もう とっくに死んでる
I'm already long dead,
透明な亡霊と対決
Confronting a transparent ghost.
痛いけれど痛い 記憶の奥
It hurts, but it's deep within my painful memories.
残念
How unfortunate.
もういないのに ありゃそっちがいいアイロニー
Even though they're gone, "Oh, that's better" is such irony.
目透かされてるのは 今の自分
The one being seen through is my current self.
ナンセンス
Nonsense.
消えない劣等イエス 弱コンプレックス
Unfading inferiority, yes, a weak complex.
取り憑かれてるみたい 泣きついたまま
It's like I'm possessed, still crying and clinging.
まだ 離れられない
I still can't let go,
ありし日の自分
Of the self from days gone by.
ああ どっかの誰かが作った
Ah, something created by someone somewhere,
シナリオに飛び乗って
I jumped onto that scenario.
期待通り 望み通り
Just as expected, just as desired,
演じてみせるわ
I'll perform it for you.
どうせなら最高にハッピーな
If anything, I'll show you a super happy,
エンディングまで連れてってよ
Ending, so take me there!
死ぬまで死なない
Won't die until I'm dead,
不滅のモンスター
An immortal monster.
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
あ、悩める人の子よ
Ah, you troubled children of man,
人ならざるものも
And those who are not human as well,
たゆまず目指せよ
Aim for it without faltering,
いつでも一途な私で
As the me who is always single-minded.
ねえ、逸らした過去も
Hey, the past you looked away from,
退屈な未来も
And the boring future too,
カウンセリング やれやれ
I'll counsel them, good grief.
古今東西 ピースピース
Peace peace, all times and places!
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
何、何、何、何、何
What, what, what, what, what?
なんだかやけに騒がしいのね
It's somehow awfully noisy, isn't it?
この頭の中
Inside this head of mine.
他人の視線 視線 視線 視線と
With others' gazes, gazes, gazes, gazes.
もう すっかり忘れた
I've completely forgotten now,
純情な正義と決別
Saying goodbye to pure-hearted justice.
甘いけれど苦い 理想の毒
Sweet but bitter, the poison of ideals.
散々
How terrible.
言われ放題の 好き勝手放題のセオリー
The theories that let people say whatever they want.
振り回されてるのは 今の自分
The one being jerked around is my current self.
当然
Naturally.
消えない劣等イエス 弱コンプレックス
Unfading inferiority, yes, a weak complex.
認めちゃえばいいわ 曝け出したまま
Just admit it, keeping it all exposed.
まだ 愛していたい
I still want to love it,
ありし日の自分
The self from days gone by.
ああ どっかの誰かが作った
Ah, something created by someone somewhere,
シナリオに飛び乗って
I jumped onto that scenario.
期待通り 望み通り
Just as expected, just as desired,
演じてみせるわ
I'll perform it for you.
どうせなら最高にハッピーな
If anything, I'll show you a super happy,
エンディングまで連れてってよ
Ending, so take me there!
死ぬまで死なない
Won't die until I'm dead,
不滅のモンスター
An immortal monster.
お望み通りの私でいましょう
I'll be the "me" that you desire.
それがあなたの救いになるのなら
If that will be your salvation.
誰も彼もが偶像を崇めて
Everyone and anyone worships idols,
救われたいと願ってるんでしょう
Wishing to be saved, right?
それなら私がその依り代になって
In that case, I'll become that vessel,
死ぬまで化かし通してあげるから
And keep tricking you until I die.
見ててね
So keep watching me.
ああ どっかの誰かが作った
Ah, something created by someone somewhere,
シナリオに飛び乗って
I jumped onto that scenario.
期待通り 望み通り
Just as expected, just as desired,
演じてみせるわ
I'll perform it for you.
どうせなら最高にハッピーな
If anything, I'll show you a super happy,
エンディングまで連れてってよ
Ending, so take me there!
死ぬまで死なない
Won't die until I'm dead,
不滅のモンスター
An immortal monster.
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
Unhappy
Unlucky
Be Happy
UNDEAD
みなさーん！こんかなたー！
Everyone! Kon-kanata!
天音かなたでーす！
It's Amane Kanata!
ホロライブ4期生の天音かなたでーす！
I'm Amane Kanata from Hololive's 4th Generation!
今日は私の誕生日ライブ「堕天使の憂鬱」に来てくれて、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to my birthday live, "Melancholy of the Fallen Angel", today!
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead
Oh my, I'm a undead
さぁ 生きている言葉
Now, living words
変わり続けることで
By continuing to change
不都合に甘んじて
Submit to inconvenience
満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied
幸せになろうと
Trying to be happy
しないなんて卑怯だ
Is just cowardly
思うままに
As you wish
期待 期待 ファンタジー
Expectation, expectation, fantasy
次は鬼枯れる
Next the demon withers
ガシャ枯れるか
Will the gacha wither?
出合って合って
Meeting and meeting
やっと始まる物語
The story that finally begins
さぁ ひと肌獣の
Now, a single skin of a beast
かたら九代ピースピース
Katara Kudai Peace Peace
なぜかどうして 未来になんて
Why and how, towards the future
なんの希望も見いだせないような気がして
I feel like I can't find any hope
もう随分生きてる
I've been living for quite a while now
既視感とテンプレで食傷
Fed up with deja vu and templates
素敵な出来事の気配もない
There's no sign of wonderful events
当然な経験の因果形が
The causal form of obvious experience
形骸化された神話と退屈な進化
A trivialized myth and tedious evolution
弱刺激が欲しいんだ
I want mild stimulation
飽きちゃった
I'm bored
慣れちゃった
I'm used to it
なんて整ってくガイダンス
What a tidy guidance
増えるコンプライアンス
Increasing compliance
蓋されてく見たい
Wanting to be covered up
吸い尽くして
Sucking dry
あれもこれもどれも
That, this, and that
同じ味がする
All taste the same
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead
Oh my, I might be error
最善も最悪も
The best and the worst
過去も未来も今にあるんだ
Both past and future are in the now
生きていることを
The fact of living
愚直に果たせよ
Fulfil it honestly
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending
死んじゃいない
I'm not dead
お前生きてるんだ
You are living
幸せを諦めてしまうな
Don't give up on happiness
人であれば
If you are human
ただ苦しみに慣れて
Just getting used to suffering
耐えているだけじゃ
And just enduring
死んでるのとしか変わらぬ
Is no different from being dead
アンデッド
Undead
目指せ生きているなら
Aim for it, if you are living
不幸に浸るのも
Indulging in misfortune
幸せになるのも
And becoming happy
想定全部お前だ
Are all up to you
古今東西大喝采
Applause from all times and places
森羅万象ピースピース
All creation, Peace Peace
人なるところ
The place where one becomes human
見積もり言辞
Talking like a leak
生き抜くものだけもの
Only those who survive
ばっかり物語
Nothing but stories
花になって
Become a Flower
影にそっと隠れようが
No matter if you hide quietly in the shadows
いいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine?
蕾のような花だって
Even a flower like a bud
あんじゃない？
Exists, right?
秘密にして守るのが
Keeping it a secret and protecting it
いいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine?
誰にも邪魔されず
Without being disturbed by anyone
華麗に咲いている
It blooms brilliantly
甘い苦いにハマんない
Don't get hooked on sweet or bitter
その判断が下んない
That judgment is not made
気に病んで下を向かないでいて
Don't worry and look down
愛に慣れちゃいない
I'm not used to love
無駄に飾らない
I don't decorate wastefully
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Even a vase made beautiful
肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need fertilizer or anything
その姿が美しい
That figure is beautiful
花になって
Become a flower
ほら 悦に浸って
Look, indulge in pleasure
その顔に
On that face
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
I get thrills and can't take my eyes off
味見して
Taste it
君に毒を盛る
I'll poison you
私も薬で
I, too, with medicine
包んであげるから
Will wrap you up
笑って
Smile
目合いたい 会いたい
I want to meet eyes, want to meet you
その笑顔に
With that smile
似合いたい 合いたい
I want to match it, want to fit
って言えば笑ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll smile if I say that
陰から支えるくらいは
Supporting from the shadows
いいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine?
欲言えばこの手で
If I'm greedy, with these hands
咲かせてみせたい
I want to show you how I can make it bloom
病のように
Like an illness
心を
The heart
食らう花
A flower that eats
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want it to wither
光が
Even if the light
届かずとも
Doesn't reach
水を
I'll continue
あげ続けるから
To give it water
いい加減に気づいて
Realize it already
君は素敵って
That you are wonderful
自惚れてもっと
Be more conceited
お大事に
Take care of yourself
無自覚なまま
Remaining unconscious
愛を蓄えて
Storing up love
綺麗にされた花瓶も
Even a vase made beautiful
肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need fertilizer or anything
その姿で咲き誇れ
Bloom proudly in that form
花になって
Become a flower
ほら 悦に浸って
Look, indulge in pleasure
その顔に
On that face
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
I get thrills and can't take my eyes off
君の毒は私の薬って
Your poison is my medicine,
包んであげるから 楽にして
I'll wrap you up, so just relax.
君の闇は私の光って
Your darkness is my light,
愛してあげるから 笑って
I'll love you, so please smile.
はい！皆そ～こんかなた～！
Hi! Hello everyone!
握力50キロ、ギュッギュッにぎりつぶしちゃうぞ、
With 50kg grip strength, I'll crush you tight,
ホロライブ4期生 かなたんこと天音かなたです！
Hololive 4th gen, Kanatan, also known as Amane Kanata!
ということでね、えー、2曲お聴きいただきましたがね、
And with that, you've just heard two songs,
今回も生誕ライブ始まってまいりました！
this birthday live has finally begun!
皆さんぜひね、ハッシュタグを
Everyone, please use the hashtag
使っていっぱいね、呟いてください、ポストしてください！
and tweet a lot, please post!
ハッシュタグはね、#天音かなた生誕ライブ でございます。
The hashtag is #天音かなた生誕ライブ.
すごいシンプルでしょ？
It's very simple, right?
ぜひね、あの、色々呟いてもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
I'd be happy if you could tweet all sorts of things!
そしてこのステージ見てください！
And look at this stage!
これすごいでしょ、めちゃめちゃ綺麗でしょ。
This is great, isn't it? It's so beautiful.
いや、なぜかと言いますとですね、今回の生誕も実はちょっとストーリーがありまして、
Well, the reason is, this birthday actually has a bit of a story,
皆さん何度も見てね、考えてほしいなと思うんですが、
and I want everyone to watch it many times and think about it,
天使と堕天使が、
an angel and a fallen angel,
まぁちょっとね、堕天使の方が世界を滅ぼしたいらしいと。
well, it seems the fallen angel wants to destroy the world.
で、天使が立ちはだかって言ってみたいな、
And the angel stands in her way,
天使が守るみたいな、世界を守るぜ、
saying the angel will protect the world,
いや、やるぜ、みたいなテーマ、戦いな感じになっておりますので、
no, I'll do it, that's the theme, it's like a battle,
ぜひその辺りも意識して歌でバトル見てくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
so I hope you'll keep that in mind and enjoy the song battle!
うわぁ、言い残したことはないかな？
Wow, is there anything else I forgot to say?
またね、あの、歌っていきますので、よろしくお願いします！
I'll be singing more, so please stay with me!
お、なんか...
Oh, something...
空が泣きそうじゃない？
Doesn't it look like the sky is about to cry?
それでは皆さん、引き続きライブをお楽しみください。
Ah, well then everyone, please continue to enjoy the live.
夢が冷めた 酔いどれ知らず
Awakened from a dream, unaware of being drunk,
争いごとは 夜が明けるまで
Quarrels until the break of dawn.
くたびれては 酷く見える
Getting tired, it looks terrible.
一千の声は 声が枯れるまで
A thousand voices, until voices run dry.
うっちゃり幸せ ずっと冷めないで
Thrown-away happiness, please don't ever cool down.
あなたの声に 耳を貸す時まで
Until the time I lend an ear to your voice.
屈する態度で 言葉さえなくて
With a submissive attitude, without even words,
体も染めて
Staining even my body.
そして 泥々 溢れ出る ほら
And then, muddy and overflowing, look,
最悪だわ
It's the worst.
腐る先まで 見るグラマー
Seeing glamour until it rots.
酩々 重ね重ね 存外
Drunkenly, over and over, unexpectedly.
さぁ 悪くないわ
Well, it's not bad.
酔いどれ知らずの 恋敵だから
Since it's a drunk-unaware love rival.
歌の声は 数知れず
Singing voices are countless,
迷い込んだら そこは君の庭
If you wander in, that's your garden.
練り歩いてる 白昼のランド
Parading through a midday land.
威勢を隠して 泥を吐けるだけ
Hiding high spirits, only able to spit mud.
如何の幸せ きっと離さないで
What kind of happiness, please don't let go.
あなたのそばに 耳を貸す時まで
By your side, until the time I lend an ear.
屈する態度で 言葉さえなくて
With a submissive attitude, without even words,
心を染めて
Staining my heart.
それは 泥々 溢れ出る ほら
That is, muddy and overflowing, look,
最悪だわ
It's the worst.
腐る私は 生きたいの
Rotting, I want to live.
酩々 重ね重ね 存外
Drunkenly, over and over, unexpectedly.
さぁ 悪くないわ
Well, it's not bad.
酔いどれ知らずの 物物語を
A drunk-unaware story.
高くそびえ、汚い言葉で誰かを傷つけた...
Towering high, you hurt someone with filthy words...
なにやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes well,
脳内戦争だもんで ずっと立って立って
It's an inner war, so I'm just standing and standing.
なにやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes well,
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me.
なにやってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes well,
nothing I do goes well.
ハッホラ 見てすごいでしょうが
Ha, look, it's amazing, isn't it?
おったまげなナイスバディが 飛び交うフィールド
A surprising nice body flying around the field.
たんたん オリジナリティ
Clack-clack, originality
どーだかなんとか模索していけって
How about searching for it somehow?
イバラでバラバラなの
Falling apart in the thorns
何個したかもわかんないお邪魔だ
I don't know how many times I've been a nuisance
良心されてんだ どうかしてるよ
Being pampered by your conscience, you're crazy
なってそっちのセリフよ
That's my line
まあいいから 全部聞き流してください どうか
Well, whatever, just let it all go in one ear and out the other, please
バカクソゴミクズ汚い言葉で誰かを傷つけた
Hurt someone with stupid, shitty, trashy, dirty words
何やってもうまくいかないの
Nothing I do goes right
脳内じゃ正義だもんね 突っ立ってたって
It's justice in your head, isn't it? Just standing there
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
第三次世界は手の込んだ犯罪
The Third World is a sophisticated crime
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
何やっても元に戻りはしない
Nothing I do will return it to how it was
だんだんとさ気づいてんだ どうかしてたって
I'm gradually realizing I was crazy
何をしても元に戻りはしない
No matter what I do, it won't return to normal
どうして どうして
Why, why?
何をしても元に戻りはしない
No matter what I do, it won't return to normal
観客は満杯だもんね 実行してたって
The audience is full, right? Even if I carried it out
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
はあ
Ha...
そっか 気づいて傷ついて そうだ
I see, realizing and getting hurt, that's it
あっという間に シチュエーションは 支離滅裂な不規則なんです
In the blink of an eye, the situation is incoherent and irregular
ダンス、ダンス、ダンスを踊れ 踊れ 満喫パーティー
Dance, dance, dance, dance! Enjoy the party
羽振らして しらばくれて ちくしょう
Acting big, playing dumb, goddamn it
一般ピープル個性だの個性だって
Ordinary people talking about individuality this and that
鉄板のネタもはや全部がご法度
The standard jokes are all taboo now
私がこれまでどれだけ努力したかしてないかに関わらないまま
Regardless of how much effort I have or haven't put in until now
独自の物差し当てがってんのよ 今に見てろクソが
You're applying your own unique yardstick. Just you wait, piece of shit
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
脳内じゃ正義だもんね 突っ立ってたって
It's justice in your head, isn't it? Just standing there
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
愛して 愛して
Love me, love me
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
第三次世界は手の込んだ犯罪
The Third World is a sophisticated crime
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
戦線は恐々だもんね 突っ立ってたって
The front lines are in trepidation, right? Just standing there
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
愛して 愛さないで
Love me, don't love me
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
心配してるフリしてんのも気づいてるよ
I've noticed you're just pretending to be worried
何やってもうまくいかない
Nothing I do goes right
何もやってないだけじゃない？
Isn't it just that you're not doing anything?
Lalalala Lalalala 誰も知らない 名もない今を 駆け抜けていくの
Lalalala Lalalala dashing through this unknown, nameless present
あの三日月に手を伸ばして
Reaching out to that crescent moon
Lalalala Lalalala 君を知りたい 声にならない 臆病な朝を
Lalalala Lalalala I want to know you, these timid mornings that have no voice
例え何度迎えようとも
No matter how many times they come
Lalalala Lalalala...
足音がパチンと切られたその時 世界と逸れてしまったみたいだ
The moment the footsteps were snapped shut, it's like I strayed from the world
目に映る景色が悲しくなれるなら 恐れずまぶたを閉じてごらん
If the scenery you see makes you sad, try closing your eyes without fear
さあ皆様こちらへどうぞ 鼓動の鳴る方へさあ
Now, everyone, step this way, towards the sound of the heartbeat
踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の踊る方へさあ
Stomp your heels, please, towards where your heart dances
蜃気楼に飛び乗って 逆さまの世界を乗りこなして
Jump onto a mirage and master this upside-down world
Lalalala Lalalala 止まない愛を知りたいと願うおまじない
Lalalala Lalalala a charm wishing to know unending love
時を超えて咲くら夜まで
Across time, until the blooming night
Lalalala Lalalala 君を知りたい何一つ見逃さぬように
Lalalala Lalalala I want to know you, so I don't miss a single thing
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one
残酷な運命が抗えぬ宿命が 考える間もなく押し寄せるなら
If cruel fate and irresistible destiny come rushing in without time to think
目が見えなくたって君を信じてみたいの 恐れずに一歩踏み出したら
Even if I can't see, I want to try believing in you. If you take a step without fear
鼓動の鳴る方へさあ 踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の踊る方へさあ
Towards the sound of the heartbeat, stomp your heels, please, towards where your heart dances
さあ皆様こちらへどうぞ 鼓動の鳴る方へさあ
Now, everyone, step this way, towards the sound of the heartbeat
踵を打ち鳴らせどうぞ 心の踊る方へさあ
Stomp your heels, please, towards where your heart dances
空飛ぶクジラに飛び乗って 逆さまの世界を踊り尽くせ
Jump onto a flying whale and dance through this upside-down world
Lalalala Lalalala 誰も知らない 名もない今を 駆け抜けていくの
Lalalala Lalalala dashing through this unknown, nameless present
あの三日月に手を伸ばして
Reaching out to that crescent moon
Lalalala Lalalala 君を知りたい 声にならない 臆病な朝を
Lalalala Lalalala I want to know you, these timid mornings that have no voice
例え何度迎えようとも
No matter how many times they come
夢ならば醒めないで 現実なんて何物でもないくらい
If it's a dream, don't wake me up, so much so that reality becomes nothing at all
時は誰も待ってくれないの
Time waits for no one
はい、皆さん。どうですか、楽しんでいただいておりますか？
Yes, everyone. Are you enjoying yourselves so far?
世界が滅びていってるわ。
The world is perishing.
滅びてますね、どんどん。困っちゃいますね。
It's perishing more and more. It's quite a problem, isn't it?
さあ、宿敵に勝つために、彼女はなんと仲間を連れてくるそうです。
Now, in order to defeat her nemesis, she's apparently bringing some friends along.
ということでこれからはゲストパートが始まっていくよ！
So, the guest part is about to begin!
それじゃあみんな、いってらっしゃい！
Well then everyone, off you go!
飛べ　起こせ　願うは自己
Fly, stir things up, what I wish for is my own ego
うん、一生一度さ　惑いと筋
Yeah, once-in-a-lifetime chance, confusion and reason
掴み負けるか　ドラマなんてないわ
Will I grasp or lose it? There's no drama
あぁ永遠　幕を開けるわ
Ah, forever opening the curtain
合致してラッキー　マネーどっちも無理　シガシガ
Winning big, lucky money, both are impossible, ego ego
光るか否か　自分次第　イダイダ
Whether I shine or not is up to me, yeah yeah
余裕で振り切り　ザ・ウェアトゼイ　ヤヤヤヨ
Easily shaking it off, we're at the top, yeah yeah
束縛　そこへ　重なるの　私だ
Being bound there, I'm the one who will win
Say my Kanataなら平常心
Say my name, Kanata, keeping my composure
My bad boy かい　don't get in my way
My bad boy, don't get in my way
CH4NGEだ　待って
Waiting for the CH4NGE
One two three, One two three
One two three, See that, See that
反目フリーズ　決めつけ投げ捨て　ノーはさ最後さ
Envy, free yourself, throw away the hesitation, it's the end
剥ぎ裂く自己　その知性　四十八計られ得ないですよ　小生グッバイ
Tearing down the ego, that intellect, can't be measured by the 48 tactics, I'm saying goodbye
あっちこっちそっち　あーこっちなっち　ヤムヤム
This way, that way, that way, this way, becoming... yum yum
満ちないこっち　満ち　ヤムヤムヤム
Incomplete here, full of it, yum yum yum
絡まりそう　でもまだ　止めないで
Entangled, but don't stop yet
アノマレそう　声々　それそれに
Anomaly, voice, voice, to each of them
Get out my way, ah ya
あんたここまで　後ろだけ見とけ
You, just look back up to this point
合致してラッキー　マネーどっちも無理　シガシガ
Winning big, lucky money, both are impossible, ego ego
光るか否か　自分次第　イダイダ
Whether I shine or not is up to me, yeah yeah
余裕で振り切り　ザ・ウェアトゼイ　ヤヤヤヨ
Easily shaking it off, we're at the top, yeah yeah
束縛　そこへ　重なるの　私だ
Being bound there, I'm the one who will win
Say my Kanataなら平常心
Say my name, Kanata, keeping my composure
My bad boy かい　don't get in my way
My bad boy, don't get in my way
CH4NGEだ　待って
Waiting for the CH4NGE
One two three... see that, see that...
短い夢を重ねて　永遠にしてゆく花の
Layering short dreams, turning them into an eternal flower
偽りが切なく　閉じ込めた命の
The lies are painful, the life that was locked away
孤独を君に捧げる　Preserved Roses
I dedicate this loneliness to you, Preserved Roses
身体の奥溢れるものを　ひとこと
A single word for what overflows deep within the body
渇いているだけ　全てが冷たく告げるなんて
Just being dry, everything telling me coldly
指も任せないで
Don't even let your fingers touch it
光と闇の　どちらにでも居れる
I can be in either light or darkness
怖がらないで　望まぬ朝はもう来ない
Don't be afraid, the morning you don't want will no longer come
鮮やかなだけを繰り返し　繋がり終わり　君はまた
Just repeating the vividness, the connection ends, and you are again
短い夢を重ねて　永遠にしてゆく花の
Layering short dreams, turning them into an eternal flower
偽りが切なく　拒む世界を傷つける
The lies are painful, hurting the world that rejects them
願うなら見せさせる　だから遠くで消えないで
If you wish, I'll let you see, so don't disappear in the distance
君が見る明日の　新しい息吹きを
The new breath of the tomorrow you see
溢した腕に迎える　離さないで
Welcoming it into my spilled arms, don't let go
無傷のまま解き出す熱を　愛を　まさぐる想い
Searching for love and the heat that starts to melt while remaining unscarred
作り物の微笑み　疑いに囚われながら
While being trapped by doubt and a fabricated smile
汚れてしまう 前に行く と決めた
I've decided to move forward before I get defiled
やがて零れて散らばる水に
In the water that will eventually spill and scatter
鮮やかに心を写し出せるなら
If I can vividly reflect my heart
捉える歌と引き換えに
In exchange for a song that captures it
激しい色を注いで
Pouring in intense colors
飾り立てた幻を
If you believe in the illusion
君が信じるなら
That I've dressed up
真実だって超えるだろう
Then it'll likely even surpass the truth
移ろう時間を止めて
Stop the fleeting time
口づけも知らないで
Without even knowing a kiss
血を流すその手は
The hands that shed blood
閉じ込めた命を
Shall offer the confined life,
孤独を君に捧げる
And its loneliness, to you
求めてる
It's what I seek
短い夢を重ねて
Piling up short-lived dreams
永遠にしていく花の
Flowers that are made eternal
偽りが切なく
Their falsehood is painful
拒む世界を傷つける
As they hurt the world that rejects them
願うなら満たせる
If you wish for it, I can fulfill it
だから遠く消えないで
So please don't vanish into the distance
君が見る明日の
Into the outstretched arms,
新しい息吹を
I welcome the new breath of life
伸ばした腕に迎える
From the tomorrow that you see
離さない
I won't let go
④責任集合合体
作詞・作曲：マサラダ
#4 Joint Responsibility Fusion
Lyrics & Music: Masarada
これは知らない
I don't know this
何も知らない
I don't know anything
何も見てない
I haven't seen anything
誰も見てない
Nobody's seen anything
空を見ても見えない夜の
Even when looking at the sky, there's nothing in the night
欠けた月にうさぎ
A rabbit in the waning moon
これはなんだ
What is this?
それがなにか
What of it?
ここは悲し
Here is sorrow
それで宜し
That's just fine
走る 逃げる 逃がす 逸らす
Running, escaping, letting go, diverting
次の欠けた場所へ
To the next waning spot
あらら…
Oh my, oh my...
妄想 止めどなく
Endless delusions
想像 咎めなく
Blameless imagination
衝動 収まらず
Uncontrollable urges
なぜか なぜか なぜか知ら
For some reason, I don't know why
最悪だ
This is the worst
おお
Ooh
寝ても覚めても付き纏う
It haunts me whether I'm awake or asleep
見えぬ意識の裏側に
On the flip side of invisible consciousness
大きく開いた黒い穴
A wide-open black hole
分かる 分かる 分かる
I get it, I get it, I get it
許す
Forgive
許せん
Unforgivable
可愛い
Cute
エー
Eh
怖い
Scary
リンゴ ゴリラ ラッパ ゴジラ
Apple, gorilla, trumpet, Godzilla
ラクダ ラボラ でも大
Camel, laboratory, but great
私たち 絶対に見てません
We definitely haven't seen it
言ってません 聞いてません
Haven't said it, haven't heard it
知ったこっちゃありません
It's none of our business
光を一視 影に一突き
A glance at the light, a jab at the shadow
許されざる思考を
Unforgivable thoughts,
当てはまらない異常を
Inapplicable anomalies,
チュチュで生きていこうじゃありませんか
Let's live through it all with a kiss, shall we?
行動 何も持たず
Acting while holding nothing
狂騒 意味もなく
Frenzied with no meaning
永劫 自己満足
Eternal self-satisfaction
だから だから だからかな
Is that why, is that why, is that why?
最高だ
This is the best
やった！
Hooray!
昔々のお思い付き
A long-ago whim
もういい無意味の人だかり
Enough with the meaningless crowd
無邪気無敵の生まれつき
Innocent and invincible by birth
それが それが それが
That is, that is, that is...
無責任集合合体
Joint Responsibility Fusion
あんたも私も関係ない
It doesn't matter for you or for me
無敵に集合体
An invincible collective
楽しくやってりゃもう満体
If we're having fun, it's all good
勝手にやってりゃ問題なし
Doing as we please, there's no problem
俺は知らない
I don't know
何も知らない
I don't know anything
何も見てない
I haven't seen anything
誰も見てない
No one has seen anything
記憶違い
A misremembering
夢の話
A story from a dream
そういうことで
And with that
それじゃあ
Goodbye
ずうっといっしょ！
Together Forever!
充電器を貸して
Lend me a charger
また貴方のせいで切らし減った
It's low again because of you
終電を見逃して
Missing the last train
また私のせいで帰れなくなった
I can't go home again because of me
繋がってようね
Let's stay connected
消耗戦に持ち込んで
Dragging it into a war of attrition
お互いに足を引っ張り合った
We pulled each other down
沈殿した思い出でずっと一緒
Together forever with settled memories
三回瞬いて
Blink three times
誰も見ていてはいない気がしたんだ
I felt like no one was watching
散々死に掛けて
Having almost died many times
夢の街に期待しないようにしてる
I try not to expect anything from the city of dreams
そうやって守った
That's how I protected
孤独さえめちゃくちゃになった
Even my loneliness was messed up
私ずっと死にたいでしかなかった
I always just wanted to die
こんな飼い殺しにしたいと思えないもの
I can't imagine wanting to keep you like this
共に過ごした日々が
The days we spent together
些細な幸せが
The small happinesses
掛け替えのないトラウマになったから今
Irreplaceable traumas became, so now
離れ離れなんて
Being apart
誰が作った言葉なんだろうね
Who came up with that word?
貴方の一生の後悔として
As your lifelong regret
添い遂げるよ
I'll be with you until the end
大切なものって何？
What is precious?
今無くしたそれ
That thing you just lost
私と間違いを犯しちゃった
You made a mistake with me
取り返しがつかないね
It's irreversible, isn't it?
健やかなるときも病めるときも
In sickness and in health
不幸、悲劇のなかで
Amidst misfortune and tragedy
ずっと一緒
Together forever
もうちょっと普通に
A little more normally
悲しいこと悲しいと思いたかった
I wanted to think of sad things as sad
症状の順に
In the order of symptoms
感情痛くして楽になりたかった
I wanted to hurt my emotions and feel better
せいぜい一生懸命に
Please try your best
聞いてくださいね
To listen to me
私いつだって死にたいでしかなかった
I always just wanted to die
貴方の言いなりになっていたくないの
I don't want to be at your beck and call
貴方だけ一人で
You alone
私の目を結んで
Blindfolding me
幸せになろうなんて思わないで
Don't think about becoming happy
髪を乾かしてくれた night かな
Was it the night you dried my hair?
私は壊されたんだよ
I was broken
貴方の一生の後悔として
As your lifelong regret
添い遂げるよ
I'll be with you until the end
外れなくなってしまった
It's become stuck
指輪みたいに
Like a ring
何度もずっとフラッシュバックしている
It keeps flashing back over and over
咲いていたいよ
I want to be in bloom
一緒にいた時のほうが
When we were together
私可愛かったら
If I was cuter then
貴方の一生の後悔として
As your lifelong regret
添い遂げるよ
I'll be with you until the end
大切なものって何？
What is precious?
今無くしたそれ
That thing you just lost
私と間違いを犯しちゃった
You made a mistake with me
取り返しがつかないね
It's irreversible, isn't it?
健やかなるときも病めるときも
In sickness and in health
他の誰かが止めるって言っても
Even if someone else tells us to stop
お揃いの名でずっと一緒
Together forever with matching names
ロストワンの号哭
The Lost One's Weeping
刃渡り数センチの不信感が
A few centimeters of blade-like distrust
挙げ句の果て静脈を刺しちゃって
Ended up stabbing a vein
病弱な愛が飛び出すもんで
And weak love came gushing out
レスポールさえ凶器に変えてしまいました
Turning even a Les Paul into a weapon
数学と理科は好きでしたが
I liked math and science
国語がどうもダメで嫌いでした
But I was bad at Japanese and hated it
正しいのがどれか悩んでいりゃ
Worrying about which one is correct
どれも正解というオチでした
It turned out they were all correct
本日の宿題は
Today's homework is
個性のない僕のこと
About me, who has no personality
過不足ない
Neither more nor less
不自由ない世間に生きたいと願って
Wishing to live in a world without constraints
どうして僕たちは　時々に　「いや　毎日」
Why do we, occasionally, "no, every day"...
悲しいって言うんだ
...say we're sad?
淋しいって言うんだ
Say we're lonely?
黒板のこの漢字が読めますか
Can you read this kanji on the blackboard?
あの子の心象は読めますか
Can you read that child's state of mind?
その心を黒く染めたのは
The one who dyed that heart black...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
そろばんのこの式が解けますか
Can you solve this formula on the abacus?
あの子の首の輪も解けますか
Can you undo the noose around that child's neck, too?
僕らこのままでいいんですか
Is it okay for us to stay like this?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what are you gonna do?
いつまで経ったって僕たちは
No matter how much time passes, we...
存在証明に酔い痴れて
...get intoxicated by proof of existence
どうしようもないくらいの嬌傲を
...an unbearable amount of arrogance...
ずっと　隠していたんだ
...we've been hiding it all along.
昨日の宿題は相変わらず解けないや
I still can't solve yesterday's homework.
過不足ない　不自由ない　最近に生きたくて
Wanting to live in these perfect, free, recent days
でもどうして僕たちの　胸元の塊は
But why does the lump in our chests...
消えたいって言うんだ
...say it wants to disappear?
死にたいって言うんだ
Says it wants to die?
黒板のこの漢字が読めますか
Can you read this kanji on the blackboard?
あの子の心象は読めますか
Can you read that child's state of mind?
その心を黒く染めたのは
The one who dyed that heart black...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
そろばんのこの式が解けますか
Can you solve this formula on the abacus?
あの子の首の輪も解けますか
Can you undo the noose around that child's neck, too?
僕らこのままでいいんですか
Is it okay for us to stay like this?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what are you gonna do?
面積比の公式言えますか
Can you state the formula for area ratio?
子供の頃の夢は言えますか
Can you state your childhood dream?
その夢すら溝に捨てたのは
The one who threw even that dream into the gutter...
おい誰なんだよ
Hey, who was it?
もう知ってんだろ
You already know, don't you?
いつになりゃ大人になれますか
When will I be able to become an adult?
そもそも大人とは一体全体何ですか
What exactly is an "adult" in the first place?
どなたに伺えばいいんですか
Who should I ask?
おいどうすんだよ
Hey, what are you gonna do?
もうどうだっていいや
Oh, whatever, it doesn't matter anymore.
はい！
Yes!
はー、皆さん、どうも！
Phew, hello everyone!
ということで皆さん見てください
So, everyone, look at this!
メガホンマイク、そしてたくさんのゲストが来てくれました。ありがとう！
The megaphone mic, and so many guests came! Thank you!
かっこいいでしょ。
It's cool, right?
どうですか。
What do you think?
かっこいいよね。
It's cool, isn't it?
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
という感じで。
And with that...
それでは皆さん。
Now, everyone.
多分ドキドキ心待ちにしていたでしょう。
I'm sure you've been waiting for this with excitement.
重大告知その1がVTRございますので
We have a VTR for Major Announcement #1,
一旦そちらを見ていただこうと思います。
so please take a look at that first.
それでは、どうぞ！
Here it is!
天音かなた 2nd Album
Amane Kanata 2nd Album
Trigger
2025.07.23 ON SALE
Keep your finger on the "Trigger".
みんなー！　アルバム出るぞー！
Everyone! The album is coming out!
Vどうでしたか？
How was the VTR?
ということでね、本当に詳細はまたこの後でという感じで
So, I'll give more details later,
ありがとうございます、皆さんのおかげで、またアルバムを出すことができました！
but thank you so much! Thanks to you all, I'm able to release another album!
そして、その後にね、もっとすごい告知もあるので絶対最後まで見てください。
And after that, there's an even bigger announcement, so make sure to watch until the end.
それではね、そちらのアルバムの中から1曲、新曲を聞いてもらいます。
Now, I'm going to perform one of the new songs from that album.
それでは聞いてください。
Please listen.
「きゅーぴっど。」
"Cupid."
何気ない声が（そわそわ）
A casual voice (fidgeting)
ちょっと不相応かな（まだまだっ）
Is it a bit out of place? (not yet)
いつからかそれが
Since when did that...
くだらない
It's pointless
気付いてんのかな　きっと甘いそんな言葉で yeah
I wonder if you've noticed? With those surely sweet words, yeah
もうハマっちゃって　ねえ矢を射っちゃって
I'm already hooked. Hey, shoot your arrow.
零から今　落ちてくどん底になにが？
Falling from zero now, to the bottom of what?
うわつく心は　わまして
Let my restless heart flutter even more.
渦巻く好意　透かして　あー
See through my swirling affection, ah.
もうキミは最低だ　かなわないな
You're really the worst. I can't beat you.
キミのキューピッドです　無我夢中
I'm your cupid, completely obsessed.
きっと夢に出てくる
I'll surely appear in your dreams.
チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ
Chu chu chu... chu chu chu... chu chu chu...
眩いの今も
You're still dazzling.
救急です　また夢遊
It's an emergency, I'm sleepwalking again.
ちょっと涙出てくる
A few tears are coming out.
チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ
Chu chu chu... chu chu chu... chu chu chu...
ぎゅっと抱きしめて！
Hold me tight!
らっぱっぱー　らっぱっぱー
Lappappaa... lappappaa...
キミはまだ知らない事情　あたしも見えてないでしょ
Circumstances you don't know yet, and I haven't seen them either, right?
なっちゃったー　なっちゃったー
Nacchattaa... nacchattaa...
あの子には見せちゃう微笑　想うだけで熱上昇
The smile I only show that person, my fever rises just by thinking of them.
ああ油断しちゃう　その眼差し　はあ
Ah, I let my guard down with that gaze, haa.
探しつづけた　宝石みたい
Like a gem I've been searching for.
でもまだまだ　ピリつく心はピンチだ
But still, my tensed heart is in a pinch.
変化するあたしも愛して
Love me even as I change.
焦げつく痛みも　あーんして　あ
Say 'ah' to the burning pain too, ah.
もうあたし最低だ　やめれないから
I'm the worst now, because I can't stop.
キミのキューピッドです　また夢中
I'm your cupid, obsessed again.
もっと欲しくなってくる
I'm starting to want more.
チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ
Chu chu chu... chu chu chu... chu chu chu...
期待もしちゃうよ
I'm starting to get expectant.
Give you らぶ　感情浮遊
Give you love, floating emotions.
ずっと気持ちあふれる
Feelings are always overflowing.
チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ　チュッチュッチュ
Chu chu chu... chu chu chu... chu chu chu...
ぎゅっと抱きしめて！
Hold me tight!
もう隠せないけど
I can't hide it anymore.
止まらない鼓動
My heartbeat won't stop.
夢から覚めて
Wake up from the dream.
気づいて　いま
Notice me, now.
2025.8.13
天音かなた 1stソロライブ
開催決定
August 13, 2025
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live
Decided to be held!
Stay Tuned...
るるる...
Ru ru ru...
すずめ feat. 十明
作詞・作曲：野田洋次郎
Suzume feat. Toka
Lyrics & Composition: Yojiro Noda
君の中にある
The red and blue lines
赤と青き線
inside of you.
それらが結ばれるのは心の臓
Where they are tied together is in the heart.
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose even in the wind.
ほどける言葉を今は育ててる
I'm nurturing words that will unravel.
時は枕に
Time as a pillow,
風は肌に
the wind on the skin,
星は産土
the stars as the guardian deity,
人は陽炎
people as heat haze.
なんで泣いてるの？と聞かれ答えれる
When asked "Why are you crying?", I can answer.
涙なんかじゃ僕ら出会えたことの意味にはまるで追いつかない
Something like tears can't even begin to catch up with the meaning of us meeting.
この火一つ
This one fire
じゃ足りない叫び
is a scream that isn't enough.
君の手に触れた時にだけ震えた　心があったよ
Only when I touched your hand,
did my heart tremble.
意味を幾つ越えれば僕らは辿り着けるのかな
How many meanings must we overcome
before we can arrive?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine.
醜さでいい
Ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で　君と手を取りたい
Beyond what is right, I want to take your hand.
思い出せない　大切な記憶
Precious memories I can't recall.
言葉にならない　ここにある想い
Feelings here that I can't put into words.
もしかしたら　もしかしたら
Maybe... Just maybe...
それだけでこの心ができている
That alone is what makes up this heart.
もしかしたら　もしかしたら
Maybe... Just maybe...
君に気付いてと今もその胸を　打ち鳴らす
Asking you to notice,
I beat against that chest even now.
何で泣いてるの？
Why are you crying?
いつか答えれる
Someday I'll be able to answer.
涙なんかじゃ　僕ら出会えたことの意味にはまるで追いつかない
Tears alone can't even begin to grasp
the meaning of our meeting.
この火一つ　じゃ足りない叫び
This one fire is a scream that isn't enough.
君の手に触れた時にだけ震えた　心があったよ
Only when I touched your hand,
did my heart tremble.
意味を幾つ越えれば僕らは辿り着けるのかな
How many meanings must we overcome
before we can arrive?
愚かさでいい
Foolishness is fine.
醜さでいい
Ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で　君と生きていきたい
Beyond what is right, I want to live with you.
皆さん天音かなた2025年生誕ライブ見てくださってありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you for watching
Amane Kanata's 2025 Birthday Live!
たくさん重大告知が発表されてわけがわからなくなっていると思うので、少しまとめて紹介します！
I'm sure you're feeling overwhelmed by all the
major announcements, so I'll summarize them!
ということでひとつめ、天音かなた2ndアルバム『Trigger』の発売が2025年7月23日水曜日に決定しましたー！
First of all, Amane Kanata's 2nd album 'Trigger'
will be released on Wednesday, July 23, 2025!
こちらはですね、完全新作全9曲入っております！
This one contains nine completely new songs!
そして、完全生産限定盤、通常盤A・Bの3形態で発売となります！
It'll be released in three versions: Limited First
Edition, and Standard Editions A and B!
そしてですね、なんとまた全国流通ということで日本中のCDショップで購入され…かれますよ！
And also, it will be distributed nationwide,
so you can buy it at CD shops all over Japan!
まずはですね、完全生産限定盤の詳細はこちらでございます！双龍さんにイラストをご担当いただきました！
First, here are the details for the Limited First
Edition! Souryuu-san provided the illustrations!
限定A4サイズボックスの超豪華パッケージの中に、『Trigger』アクリルスタンド、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PRカード「天音かなた」、秘密の特訓ノート、そしてCDが入っております！
Inside the deluxe A4-sized box are an acrylic
stand, a PR Card, a Training Notebook, and the CD!
アクスタはアルバム3種すべてのイラストを使用したミニアクスタ、ホロカデザインは通常盤Aデザインの押しおしおママのイラストを使った限定デザイン！
The acrylic stand is a mini version, and the Holoca
card is a limited design by Oshio-mama!
そして秘密の特訓ノートには僕が実際レコーディングで使った歌詞、メモ入りの歌詞の資料やアルバムの制作日記、そしてみんなへのお手紙も入っております！
The Notebook has my recording notes, lyrics,
a production diary, and a letter to all of you!
そして通常盤はこちらの2種！通常盤Aは我らが押しおしお先生、ママですね！のイラスト！
Here are the two Standard Editions! Edition A
features an illustration by Oshio-mama!
そして通常盤Bは前回のアルバムに引き続き、平山寛菜先生にお願いいたしました！
For Edition B, we asked Kanna Hirayama-sensei
again, following the previous album!
どちらも特典透明三方背スリーブに入っております！
Both come in a special transparent
three-sided sleeve!
そしてですね、今回も通常盤A・Bにはランダムアナザージャケット全6種類のうち1枚がついてきます！
Also, Editions A and B will include one of six
random 'another jackets'!
そしてそして！数量限定で僕の直筆サインが入っているかも！ということらしいです、ぜひどちらも手に入れてください！
And there's a chance of getting an autographed
one in limited quantities! Please get both!
そして各店舗の購入特典ももちろん大充実していますので、みんなどれにするかじっくり決めてください！
The store bonuses are also great, so please
take your time deciding which one to get!
本日この後配信が終わり次第、予約開始です！
Pre-orders will start as soon as
this broadcast ends today!
そして1点、hololive OFFICIAL SHOPのアルバム購入についての注意事項です。完全生産限定盤は発売日までのお届けとなりますが、
A note on the Hololive Official Shop: The Limited
Edition will be delivered by the release date, but...
2ndアルバム通常盤以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入はできません。
...items other than the standard edition cannot be
purchased at the same time.
通常盤は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが、店頭発売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるのでご注意ください。詳しくは販売サイトの注意事項をご確認ください。
Standard editions can be combined, but delivery
may be later. Check the site for details.
ということでこれややこしすぎるので、明日ね、あの配信で…
This is too complicated, so I'll explain more
during a stream tomorrow...
詳しい説明いたします。
I will explain in detail.
そしてもう一つの重大告知！
And one more major announcement!
天音かなた、2025年8月13日に、
Amane Kanata's first solo live is set to be held
ファーストソロライブの開催が決定しました！
on August 13th, 2025!
やった！来たー！
Yay! It's here!
ということでですね、ライブ会場やチケット、
So, detailed information about the live venue,
グッズなどの詳しい情報はまた改めて発表しますので、
tickets, and goods will be announced at a later date,
お前らとりあえず、
everyone, for now,
8月13日水曜日を空けておいてください！
please keep Wednesday, August 13th open!
それから3つ目。本日解禁いたしました新曲「きゃぴっど」は、
Next, the third one. The new song "Cupid," revealed today,
TeddyLoidさんに制作いただいております。
is produced by TeddyLoid.
セカンドアルバムにももちろん入ります。
Of course, it will also be included in the second album.
そしてこのあとMV公開して、
The music video will be released after this,
24時から配信リリースもいたしますので、ぜひチェックしてください。
and it will also be available for streaming starting at midnight, so please check it out.
ライブとアルバムはハッシュタグ
We have a hashtag for the live and album,
「#撃ち抜けかなた」というものがありますので、感想どしどしお待ちしております。
"#ShootThroughKanata," so we're looking forward to your feedback.
アルバム配信が終わり次第、
Once the album streaming starts,
受付、予約受付開始なので、ぜひチェックしてください。
pre-orders will open, so please check it out.
そして4つ目、天音かなた誕生日記念2025のグッズ出まーす！
And the fourth one, Amane Kanata birthday celebration 2025 goods are coming out!
誕生日記念フルセットはこんな感じになっておりまして、一つずつ紹介したいと思います。
The birthday celebration full set looks like this, and I'd like to introduce them one by one.
まずはアクリルスタンド。これ、みんなとお忍びデート中、で、
First, the acrylic stand. This is for an incognito date with everyone,
グッズで、パーカー、あ、それともお揃いのやつ着てるから、
with goods, the parker... oh, or rather, since we're wearing matching ones,
みんなグッズ買ってくれたらこれお揃いになります、そのパーカーは。
if everyone buys the goods, we'll be matching in that parker.
次はこちら、かなパーカー。かなたその雰囲気も入って、
Next is this, Kana-Parker. It incorporates Kanata's vibe,
すごくおしゃれな感じでイラストも背中にめっちゃデカく付いています。
it's very stylish, and there's a huge illustration on the back.
みんなとお揃いになるから、ぜひよろしくお願いします。
It'll be matching with everyone, so thank you.
みんなじゃなくてかなたそとお揃いね！ね！
Not with everyone, but matching with Kanata! Right!
3つ目は、推し活がはかどるポーチ。
Third is the "Oshikatsu" (fan activities) pouch.
これは小さいぬいぐるみとかキーホルダーとか入れられるクリアポケットに、
This has a clear pocket for small plushies or keychains,
缶バッジも入れられるし、リュックとかにも引っ掛けられるからカスタムしてね。
you can also put badges in it, and it can be attached to a backpack, so please customize it.
次は「かなたそ推しだよね？」バッジ。
Next is the "You're a Kanata fan, right?" badge.
はい、こちら僕推しの平民のためのバッジ。
Yes, this is a badge for the commoners who support me.
かなたそ推しね、えーとかなたそちゃんとウパを両方付いています。
For Kanata fans, uh, both Kanata-chan and the axolotl mascot are on it.
この文字のところとかなたそちゃんとウパのところはなんか、
The letters and the parts with Kanata-chan and the mascot
半立体らしい。すごい可愛いぜ。
are apparently semi-3D. It's so cute.
そしてポストカードがフルセット購入特典で付いてきます。
And a postcard comes as a full set purchase bonus.
ここには直筆サインが入りますが、この直筆サインはね、
It will be autographed, and as for these autographs,
今回ね、全員に書かせていただきますので、頼よろでございます。
I'll be signing them for everyone this time, so please look forward to it.
そしてホロカのPRカードも付いてくるよ。
And a HoloCArd PR card also comes with it.
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、
As a full set bonus for the talent premium goods,
2024年9月から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚付きます。
it includes one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game released in September 2024.
同梱するカードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入されたお客様のみ対象となります。
The included card is only for customers who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのはゲームで1枚だけ使用でき、推しをアピールできるキーカード「推しホロメンカード」です。
The bonus is an "Oshi Holomen Card," a key card that can be used once per game to show off your favorite member.
カードの詳細や遊び方については、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの公式ホームページにてご確認ください。
For card details and how to play, please check the Hololive Official Card Game official website.
同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなりますので、ご了ください。
Please note that the included card will only be in Japanese.
ということでね、さすがのかなたそももう口が回らなくなってきていますが、
So, even the great Kanata is starting to get tongue-tied,
皆さん付いてこれていましたでしょうか。
but were you all able to keep up?
ぜひぜひね、たくさん重大告知ありましたが、いろいろ整理して、
There were a lot of major announcements, so please sort through them,
皆さんぜひ全てチェックしてもらえたら嬉しいなと思います。それではまた明日お会いしましょう、バイバーイ！
and I'd be happy if you could check all of them. Well then, see you again tomorrow! Bye-bye!